If you're also tired of web designs that all look the same, you know, that generic AI vibe...
and want to create these kinds of advanced, dynamic effects,
So, these three secrets will get you started from scratch.
sick web animations
And all without writing a single line of code.
I'm Huang Bai, a designer who's pretty good with AI.
1. 3D Models
So, if you want to add these kinds of interactive 3D elements,
First, you can head over to this website.
It's packed with tons of ready-to-use 3D assets.
Just pick one, export the code, and then paste it into Kimi.
And make sure you select the 'AI Agent' mode.
The front-end design agent won't just place the 3D element for you,
and it will automatically analyze the model,
and generate interactive effects that are perfect for your website.
2. Layering Animations
An overlay effect like this one.
This makes it perfect for building a personal website.
You can just enter this prompt.
Using Kimi's built-in image generation model, create the following two images.
Then, enter this prompt.
Kimi doesn't just generate websites quickly.
and even publish it with a single click.
It can even set up its own database and backend for you.
And just like that, you'll have a complete personal website.
3. Video Backgrounds.
And for these really atmospheric, animated backgrounds...
So, once you have the video generated by AI, you can just feed it this prompt.
The AI will then anchor the video's progress.
Then, just have the AI adjust the settings,
And just like that, you can create a parallax scrolling effect like this.
Follow me to learn more cool AI tricks.